export const questionsAndAnswers = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "Which of the following is correct about callbacks?",
    options: [
      "A callback is a function that passes to another function as an argument.",
      "A callback is not a function that passes to another function as an argument",
      "None of above",
    ],
    answer: [
      "A callback is a function that passes to another function as an argument.",
    ],
  },

  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number?",
    options: ["toString()", "toFixed()", "toLocaleString()", "toPrecision()"],
    answer: "toString()",
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "If we declare a variable, let test = 1, then reassign it to test = 2, what will happen?",
    options: [
      "test will equal 2",
      "test will equal 1",
      "a TypeError will occur",
      "test will equal undefined",
    ],
    answer: "test will equal 2",
  },

  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What does `undefined` mean in JavaScript?",
    options: [
      "undefined means a variable has been declared but has not yet been assigned a value",
      "undefined means function didnâ€™t return any value",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "How do you find out which character occurs at the 5th position in a string `How are you`?",
    options: ["Substring()", " String()", "Stringlength()", " CharAt()"],
    answer: "CharAt()",
  },

  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "How do you prompt users with messages and at the same time requesting user input?",
    options: ["Alert()", "Display()", " Prompt()", "Confirm()"],
    answer: "Prompt()",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "How to debug a code in JavaScript?",
    options: [
      "Use breakpoints on Chrome DevTool",
      "console.log()",
      "debugger",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is the difference between an agrument and a parameter?",
    options: [
      "Agrument is a variable declared in a function, but parameter is an actual value that is passed to the function",
      "Parameter is a variable declared in a function, but agrument is an actual value that is passed to the function",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer:
      "Parameter is a variable declared in a function, but agrument is an actual value that is passed to the function",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "setTimeOut() is executed by Web API",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Javascript is not asynchronous",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is new in ES6?",
    options: [
      "Symbol data type",
      "Let and const keyword",
      "Arrow function",
      "B and C, but not A",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What is lexical scope?",
    options: [
      "A variable that can be accessed by all other functions",
      "A variable that can only be determined by the region where it's created and defined",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer:
      "A variable that can only be determined by the region where it's created and defined",
  },
];
